simplymeasured.com 2012-12-22

# Simply Measured, Inc – Privacy Policy | Simply Measured

**Last Updated:** September 1, 2011 ****

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**

The Simply Measured website and services made available from SimplyMeasured.com, RowFeeder.com, Export.ly or otherwise by Simply Measured are owned and operated by Simply Measured, Inc. (“ **Simply Measured** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **our** ,” or “ **us** ”). At Simply Measured, we understand that you value your privacy, and we want to help make your experience with our site and services (referred to in this policy collectively as our “ **Services** ”) satisfying and safe. This policy describes our collection of information, including personal information, in connection with our Services, and explains how we use and disclose this information. To make this policy easy to find, we make it available from our homepage.

**Personal Information**

“ **Personal information** ,” as used in this policy, is information that may be used to identify an individual, such as a person’s name, email address, or credit card number.

**How We Collect Personal Information**

We collect personal information in the course of providing our Services to you, including through your voluntary, optional submissions, such as information that you provide to us at the time of registering for our Services, or through your use of our Services. When you register with us for an account, we may collect information such as your name and email address. When you pay for certain features of the Services, we may collect information such as your credit card number, expiration date, billing address, and CVV or security code number. You may also provide personal information to us in other ways, such as by requesting user support.

We may receive personal information from third parties about their users, and may combine this information with other personal information we maintain about you. If we do so, this policy also governs the combined information.

**How We Use Personal Information**

We use personal information we collect to provide, improve, and develop our Services, to tailor your user experience, to respond to your inquiries or requests, to prevent or investigate fraudulent or inappropriate usage of our Services, for research and development, to analyze trends, and for the other purposes described in this policy.

In addition, we may use your email address to deliver product information and marketing messages. You may opt-out from receiving these marketing messages by following the instructions provided in the messages to unsubscribe from email communication or by emailing the address provided at the end of this policy.

**How We Share Personal Information**

We may also provide personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, and other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of providing our Services and for our other purposes described in this policy. We limit the personal information shared with these third parties to that which is necessary to carry out those functions.

We may share personal information with third parties (including regulatory or law enforcement authorities) in order to carry out a user’s request or if we believe that doing so is legally required or is in our interest to protect our property or other legal rights (including, but not limited to, enforcement of our agreements), or the rights or property of others.

**If you post any of your information to a public area of our Services, please be aware that it is no longer “personal information” for the purposes of this policy, and we or anyone else may use such information without restriction. If you provide access to personal or other information , including your email address or name, to a limited set of other users through any of our privacy controls or other settings, please understand that Simply Measured has no control over how others may collect, use, or disclose such information.**

**Non-Personal Information We Collect, and How We Use It**

We may also collect information that is not personally identifiable, and may aggregate personal information or otherwise render it anonymous (that is, non-personally identifiable). We may use non-personally identifiable information we collect to provide, improve, and develop our Services and otherwise to tailor your user experience, to prevent or investigate fraudulent or inappropriate usage of our Services, for research and development, and for the other purposes described in this policy. We may use this anonymous information for various purposes and may share it with third parties. Below are some examples of the types of non-personal information we collect and some specific examples of how we use this information:

  * **_Usage tracking_** **.** We may collect non-personal information from your use of our Services. For example, we may collect information about user traffic and usage patterns throughout our site, and similar information regarding the use of our Services. We may also track click-through information, such as IP addresses, from the messages we send to our users. We use the information we collect in these manners to, for example, improve our Services, to develop new products and services, to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns, to discourage and address abusive and fraudulent use of our Services, and to help our users with troubleshooting issues.

  * **_Methods of collection_** **.** We collect non-personal information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “Web beacons”). When you visit our site or use our Services, we may send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser or recognizes a cookie that is already on your machine. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, and to customize your experience. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Also, please be aware that third parties may set cookies on your hard drive or use other means of passively collecting information about your use of their services or content. We do not have access to, or control over, these third-party means of passive data collection.

If we directly combine any non-personal information gathered through passive means with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information under this policy. Otherwise, we use information collected by passive means in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable forms.

**Children**

Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requiring parental consent. Any person who provides his or her personal information to us through our Services represents that he or she is older than 12 years of age.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Please be aware, however, that no data transmissions over the Internet or other networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security or integrity of any information you transmit to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk. Once we receive personal information, we make reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. But we cannot represent or guarantee that personal information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed.

If Simply Measured learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Simply Measured may post a notice through the Services if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to access the Services. Simply Measured may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

**Third-Party Sites and Services**

Our Services may contain links to and interoperate with third-party sites and services. Any links to or interoperability with third-party sites or services are provided for your convenience only, and we do not have control over the content or privacy and security practices and policies of such third parties. Any personal information that you provide to any other third party is subject to that third party’s privacy practices and policies, not this policy. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

**Business Transfers**

Information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, or similar transaction, as well as in the unlikely event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which personal information would be transferred as one of our business assets.

**International Visitors**

The Services are hosted in and provided from the United States. If you use our Services from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States. The United States does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and some other regions. By providing your personal information, you consent to the transfer of your personal data to the United States and the use of your personal information, in accordance with this policy.

**Information Retention and Disposal**

We may retain personal information for as long as we have a business need for it or as applicable laws or regulations or government orders require us to retain it. Additionally, the Service may enable you (or other users) to save information including information that you have made public or allowed certain users to access or see.

**Changes and Updates**

We may occasionally update this policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of this policy. We encourage you to review this policy periodically to stay informed about our collection, use, and disclosure of personal information.

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us using the following contact information:

**Simply Measured, Inc.**  
**1507 Belmont Ave**  
**Suite 200**  
**Seattle, WA 98122**  
**us@simplymeasured.com**
